有趣邮政小知识
Oh, here's a fun postal fact.
邮箱的内部是受联邦政府管辖
The inside of our mailbox is under federal jurisdiction,
所以如果你伤了我的右拇指
so if you broke my right thumb,
是帕萨迪纳市警局抓你
that's the Pasadena City Police.
但如果你此时伤了我的左拇指
But if you broke my left thumb,
那就是联邦调查局抓你
that's the FBI.
如果我真要犯事入狱
If I'm going to jail,
那怎么也得杀了他  而不是伤他拇指
I'm killing him, not breaking his thumb.
没错
Yeah.
我收到我姥姥给我寄的信
I got a letter from my meemaw.
闻闻
Smell this.
什么味道
What is that?
玫瑰  酸痛药膏  脚气药粉
Uh, roses, Bengay and Dr. Scholl's Foot Powder.
CK牌姥姥味香水
Yep. Grandma By Calvin Klein.
我上一次收到手写的信
You know, the last time I got a handwritten letter
是某人投诉我停车技术像瞎子
was from someone who told me I park like a blind person.
那个某人有名字的好吗
That someone has a name.
谢谢
Uh, thank you.
姥姥弄了一副新假牙
Oh, Meemaw got a new set of teeth.
可后来她又找到她旧的那副了
Oh, but then she found her old ones.
所以新的就成了她上教堂专用假牙
Oh, so, now the new ones are just gonna be her church teeth.
有意思
Fun.
就像你的漫展史波克耳朵
Like your Comic-Con Spock ears,
跟在家戴的史波克耳朵一样
and your around-the-house Spock ears.
我停车技术明明还行
I park fine.
天啊  她要来看我
Oh, my goodness, she's coming to visit!
很好啊  终于能见到她本人
Oh, it'll be nice to finally meet her.
你们绝对会爱死她
Oh, you are going to love her.
她会是你们见过最善良最贴心的女人
She is the kindest, sweetest woman you'll ever meet.
除非你是挖她菜园的地鼠
Yeah, unless you're a gopher digging up her vegetable garden.
那样的话  就等着
In that case, you can expect
脑袋被她用铲子打爆吧
to have your head bashed in with a shovel.
翻译：恭喜发财赛太公  红包拿给YY猫
猫中之王  别扭大菜
不是她  不是她
That's not her. That's not her.
这也不是她  不是她
不是她
That's not her.
不是她  不是她
That's not her. That's not her.
那也不是她
That's not her.
真的吗
dort dort dort Really?
那个亚洲老头不是你姥姥吗
The old Asian man is not your Meemaw?
你这话也没有帮助
And that's not helpful.
我圣诞节时送了她个苹果手机
You know, I-I got her an iPhone for Christmas.
我查看一下她的地点
I'll see where she is.
那挺不错呀
Oh, that's nice.
她那个年纪的大多数人都不愿意接受新科技
Most people her age don't embrace technology.
她自己不知道她有苹果手机
Oh, no, she doesn't even know she has it.
我让我姐塞进她的包里
No, I had my sister slip it in her bag
这样我就能追踪海龟一样追踪她
so that I can track her like a sea turtle.
就像我们在动物园弄丢你时一样
Same as when we lost you at the zoo.
我都说几百次了
Uh, for the hundredth time,
我闻到爆米花的味道  但找不到摊位
I smelled kettle corn and couldn't find the cart.
但还是解释不了
Still doesn't explain
你最后怎么跑上高速分隔带上
how you ended up on the freeway divider.
小甜饼
Moon Pie!
姥姥
Meemaw!
我好高兴看到你
I'm so happy to see you!
我也很高兴看到你啊
I'm so happy to see you, too!
你变得更小个了
You got even smaller.
我喜欢
I love it!
姥姥  这位是莱纳德
Uh, Meemaw, this is Leonard.
莱纳德  这是我姥姥
Leonard, this is my Meemaw.
您好  很高兴终于见到您了
Hi. So nice to finally meet you.
姥姥  让我来帮您拿行李吧
Let me take this for you, Meemaw.
谢谢
Thank you.
别乱叫  你只能叫她"康斯坦丝"
No. Oh, no. Now you call her "Constance."
我才能叫她"姥姥"
I call her "Meemaw."
你自己有你自己的姥姥
You have your own Meemaw.
你四岁时她就去世了可不是我的错
It's not my fault she died when you were four.
这么对朋友说话合适吗
Is that nice to say to your friend?
不合适  姥姥
It isn't, Meemaw.
莱纳德  对不起
Sorry, Leonard.
您能在我们那里长住下去吗
Can you please live with us forever?
太扯了吧  如果你有超能力
That's ridiculous! If you had a superpower,
而且穷尽一生想将其压制住
and spent your whole life being told to suppress it,
当你最后决定要接受这能力了
when you finally decide to embrace that power,
为毛独自躲去荒山野岭
why hide in isolation?!
真是不好意思
I'm sorry,
请问你这版本的
and how much money did
《冰雪奇缘》赚了多少钱呢
your version of Frozen make?!
我只是认为
I'm just saying,
与其唱《随它吧》  她真正该唱的是
instead of "Let it Go," She should really sing,
《看我像根巧克力棒躲冰箱里》
"Look At Me Hiding in a Freezer Like a Dove Bar."
她在一天里造了一座冰雪城堡  化雪成兵
She built an ice castle, made a snow monster
还将自己彻底改头换面
and gave herself a complete makeover in one day.
你知道你今天都干嘛了吗
You know what I saw you do today?
打开锡箔包装  直接吃了一整块奶油干酪
Eat a block of cream cheese straight from the foil
而且还对自己老婆隐瞒实情
and lie about it to your wife!
抱歉偷听到你们的对话  你们知道
Sorry for eavesdropping, but did you know
他们是先有《随它吧》这首歌
they actually had the song "Let It Go" in place
之后才定下完整故事的吗
before they finalized the story?
这是真的
Yeah, that's true.
其实  他们因为太爱这首歌
In fact, they liked the song so much,
他们把修改剧本来配这首歌
they retooled the whole script around it.
这也是为啥这部片这么烂
Which is probably why that movie sucks.
我们在这聊"冰雪"
Here we are talking about Frozen,
但你还被呛到火烧火燎
and yet, you got burned.
小姐  抱歉
Miss, I'm so sorry.
你怎么会不喜欢那部电影呢
How can you not like that movie?
我只是觉得它名过其实
I just think it gets more credit than it deserves.
我一小时前就这么说了
Oh, that's what I said an hour ago.
你们俩聊了一个小时《冰雪奇缘》吗
Wow. You've been talking about Frozen for an hour?
你应该听我们聊动画片《恐龙当家》
You should've seen us after The Good Dinosaur.
这是部设定在后侏罗纪时期的西部风格片
It was a classic western set in the post-Jurassic period,
它完全改变了我的人生
and it changed my life.
你舒服吗
Are you comfortable?
非常舒服
Very.
休息挺好的
It's nice to rest
尤其是在走完八百阶楼梯后
after 800 flights of stairs.
你刚才可爱死了  气喘吁吁
You were so cute, huffin' and puffin'.
艾米来了
There's Amy.
我要告诉你  你们绝对合得来
I just know you're gonna hit it off.
因为你俩的时尚品味一模一样
You both have the same fashion sense.
进来吧  跟姥姥请安
Hello! Come in, say hi to my Meemaw.
很高兴见到您
Hi. Nice to meet you.
我也是
Nice to meet you, too.
旅途还好吗
How was your trip?
非常棒
Wonderful.
机长技术非常好
And the pilot did such a good job,
我还送他一颗奶油糖
I gave him a butterscotch.
那太好了
That's great.
瞧瞧您  坐在谢尔顿的专座上
And look at you, sitting in Sheldon's spot.
-他从来都没让我坐过  -是啊
- You know, I don't even get to sit there. - Yeah.
你这辈子都没机会坐
And you never will.
对了  问她要纸巾
Ooh, hey, oh, ask her to do the tissue thing.
去吧  问她
Do it, ask her.
能给我张纸巾吗
Can I have a tissue?
当然
Of course.
是不是超级棒
Isn't that the best?!
她就像蜘蛛侠奶奶
She's like Grandma Spider-Man.
他从小就这么说我
He's been saying that since he was little.
我到现在还不知道是什么意思
I still don't know what it means.
你们俩坐下好好了解彼此
Oh, well, you two sit down and get to know each other.
我去帮你准备好房间
I'll get your room ready.
你不许翻我的行李箱找礼物
Oh, now don't you go looking through my suitcase for presents.
如果我翻了  会找到礼物吗
If I did, would I find any?
或许吧
Maybe.
但你还会找到我的阿嬷胸罩和内裤
But you also might find my brassieres and bloomers.
我愿意冒这个险
That's a risk I'm willing to take!
这真是太好了
Well, this is so nice.
您的到来让他欣喜若狂
He's so excited to have you here and...
好了  我就不跟你拐弯抹角兜圈子了
Okay, now let's you and me get something straight.
他或许以为我是来给他做饼干的
He may think that I came to bake him cookies,
但我来的真正原因是要掂掂你的斤两
but the real reason is to size you up.
掂掂...我的斤两
Si-Size me up?
谢尔顿的母亲或许对你没意见
Sheldon's mother may be okay with you,
但我可没这么好说话
but I'm not so easy.
我...
Well, I-I'm...
我相信一旦您了解我  会喜欢我的
I'm sure you'll like me once you get to know me.
你最好希望如此
Oh, you better hope so.
德州特色运牛车载运列车套装
A Texas Special cattle and calf car train set
还有真的喇叭和铃铛
with authentic horn and bell!
谢谢  外婆
Thank you, Meemaw!
不用客气  小饼干
Oh, you're welcome, Moon Pie.
艾米  你为什么看起来不兴奋
Amy, why don't you look excited?
你得到看我玩这个的机会呢
Well, you get to watch me play with this!
我看你在读《传奇系列》
Oh, I see you're reading Saga.
对  听说这系列很不错
Yeah, I hear it's pretty good.
的确  很少有漫画的封面是
It is, and not a lot of comics have a woman with wings
一位有翅膀的女人在给孩子喂奶
breastfeeding a baby right on the cover.
你这么说了  我就看看吧
I'll take your word for it.
你的确该看
You should.
他真的仔细看过了
He's really looked.
对了  我是拉杰
I'm Raj, by the way.
-他是霍华德  -你好
- This is Howard. - Hi.
我是克莱儿
Claire.
我从来没在这里见过你  克莱儿
Well, I've never seen you here before, Claire.
今天是我第一次来
It's my first time.
我在为我写的一部电影寻找灵感
I'm looking for inspiration for this movie I'm writing.
你是编剧吗
You're a screenwriter?
编剧兼酒保
Well, screenwriter, slash bartender,
兼  再过一个月就得住在车里的人
slash, a month away from living in my car.
我懂
Yeah, I get that.
我是科学家
I'm a scientist,
兼派对策划师
slash party planner,
兼小型犬爱好者
slash small-dog enthusiast,
兼...
slash...
说了"科学家"后就应该打住的人
guy who probably should have stopped at "scientist."
你真的是科学家吗
You're really a scientist?
天体物理学家
Well, astrophysicist.
太好了
That's perfect.
我能找个时间请你指教一下我的电影吗
Do you think I could pick your brain for my movie some time?
是给孩子看的动画科幻片
It's animated sci-fi for kids.
当然  我喜欢动画片
Sure. I love animated movies.
没错
He does,
他的《星际宝贝》收集瓷盘可以证明这一点
and he has the Lilo & Stitch collector plates to prove it.
抱歉我想为人生添加一点点小魔力
Excuse me for wanting a little magic in my life.
这是我的电话号码
Here's my number.
打给我  我们出来坐坐
Give me a call, we'll get together.
-好的  -再见
- Yeah, great. - See ya.
再见
Yeah, bye.
你这是干什么
What are you doing?
你可是有女朋友的人
You have a girlfriend.
所以呢
So?
所以
So,
你觉得她知道你帮一位美女
how do you think she'd feel about you
创作剧本  她会作何感想
helping a beautiful girl with her screenplay?
我没觉得她算美女吧
I wouldn't say she's beautiful.
真的吗  你不觉得她迷人吗
Really? You don't think she's attractive?
觉得啊  我只是不会跟女朋友说而已
I do. I just wouldn't tell my girlfriend.
康斯坦丝  您确定不用我给您倒点红酒吗
Constance, are you sure I can't pour you some wine?
不用给我倒红酒了
Oh, no wine for me.
谢尔顿去给我拿威士忌了
Sheldon's bringing me my whiskey.
酒来了  外婆
Here you go, Meemaw.
严格按照您的喜好
I made it just how you like--
倒了一大杯
a lot in a glass.
谢谢  小甜饼
Thank you, Moon Pie.
我很好奇
Um, curious.
您为什么叫谢尔顿"小甜饼"
Why do you call Sheldon "Moon Pie?"
因为他美味可人
'Cause he's so nummy-nummy.
她想把他一口吃掉
She could just eat him up.
我叫她"姥姥"
And I call her "Meemaw,"
是因为  你们看她就知道了
because, well, just, well, look at her.
真有意思
It's interesting that
莱纳德和佩妮都知道他昵称的由来
Leonard and Penny know about his nickname
而你却不知道
and you don't.
话说回来
Oh, well, you know,
现在听你们这么一说  我好像有点印象了
now-now that I'm hearing it, it does sound familiar.
怎么可能
How could it?
我从来没跟你说过  你也从来没问过
I never told you, and you never bothered to ask.
我现在知道了
Well, now I know.
佩妮  我得知你有一份新工作
So, Penny, I understand you have a new job.
是的
Yes.
我现在是一名医药销售
I'm a pharmaceutical sales rep.
你们现代女性要啥有啥  真棒
It's so wonderful that you modern gals can have it all.
有丈夫  还能有一份全职工作
A husband and a full-time career.
我也有一个男朋友和一份全职工作啊
I have a relationship and a full-time career, too.
那不是什么好事
That doesn't bode well.
为什么  她有工作你就说好
Why not? You-you just said it's okay for her to work.
莱纳德不像谢尔顿那么需要人照顾
Well, Leonard doesn't need as much tending to as Sheldon does.
而且小甜饼跟我解释过
And as Moon Pie explained,
莱纳德的工作更像是爱好
Leonard's work is more of a hobby.
-真是我"最好的朋友"  -是啊
- That's my best friend. - Yeah.
我知道您很呵护你的外孙
Look, I-I get that you're protective of your grandson,
但他已经是个成年人了
but he's an adult now.
也许我比您更懂得他的所需所求
Maybe I understand what he needs better than you do.
我感谢你的坦诚相待  宝贝
I appreciate your honesty, dear.
谢谢
Thank you.
让我也对你推心置腹地说一句
And here's some more honesty:
我不怎么喜欢你
I don't like you very much.
也许我也不喜欢你啊
Well, maybe I don't like you either.
不  不  不行
No, no, no, no, no,
这样不行  你们必须互相喜欢
no, no, no. Y-You have to like each other.
我们4点半还订了苹果蜂餐馆呢
Well, we have a 4:30 reservation at Applebee's.
我想我该走了
I think I should leave.
为什么啊
But why?
除了你俩吵架这事
Other than you two fighting,
其他都挺好的啊
we're having such a good time.
你一离开客厅  你亲爱的姥姥
The minute you left the room, your precious meemaw
就开始给我脸色看
started giving me a really hard time.
我才不要受这气
I don't need this.
让她走吧
Let her go.
还有  无论如何你也不许
And under no circumstance
把那个订婚戒指给她
will you give her that engagement ring.
什么戒指
What ring?
也许我们应该回避一下
Maybe we should give them some privacy.
好的  好的
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
你先走  我一会就来
You go ahead. I'll catch up with you.
你有一枚订婚戒指吗
You have an engagement ring?
是的
Yes.
佩妮  你知道这件事吗
Penny, did you know about this?
好  我们走吧
All right, let's go.
你什么时候准备的订婚戒指
When did you get an engagement ring?
我妈妈给我的
My mother gave it to me,
我一直在考虑把它给你
and I had been thinking about giving it to you,
结果我们分手了
but then we broke up.
感谢天  感谢地
Well, thank goodness for that.
谢尔顿  请你告诉你姥姥
Sheldon, will you please tell your grandmother
别插手这件事好嘛
to stay out of this?
那我做不到
Oh, I don't think I could do that.
谢尔顿  告诉那个姑娘
Sheldon, tell this girl
我的戒指永远不可能戴在她手上
that my ring will never be on her finger.
你... 这我也做不到啊
Y...I'm gonna opt out of that one, too.
谁说我想要和他订婚了
Who said I even want to be engaged to him?
而且就算我愿意  我也不需要你的旧货
And if I do, I-I don't need your hand-me-downs!
好吧  好吧
All right, all right!
我们还是...
Look, l-let's all...
我们还是冷静下来
let's remain calm
好好分析一下目前的情况
and analyze this situation.
我明白你们俩才刚刚认识
Now, I realize that you've only known each other
不到一天
for less than a day,
但你们如此暴躁  是否有可能是因为
but is it possible this crankiness is because
你俩月经周期刚好同步了呢
your cycles have synced?
你出去
You leave the room
让我们大人说话
and let the grown-ups talk.
赶紧的
Now.
别像说小孩那样说他
Don't speak to him like he's a child.
谢谢你帮我撑腰
Thank you.
我要去隔壁和莱纳德一起玩了
I'm gonna go next door and play with Leonard.
所以你遇到一个姑娘  交换了电话号码
Okay, so you met this girl, you exchanged numbers,
然后还要和她再见面
and you're gonna meet up with her.
只是为了帮她完成剧本而已
Just to help her with her screenplay.
这样应该没什么问题
Oh. Well, I guess that's not so bad.
你当时不在现场
You weren't there.
他一直在撩人家
He was really flirting.
如果美国妞们钟爱我这样
Hey, it's not my fault if American women project
声音扣人心弦
their fantasies on foreigners
又帮人实现愿望异国精灵  那也不是我的错啊
with the kind of magical voice that grants wishes.
我想这无伤大雅
I'm sure it was harmless.
人人都会互撩  不是大问题
People flirt. No big deal.
真的吗  那如果我也...
Really? So it's okay if I fl...
你不行  你是我的小奴
Not you. I own your ass.
关键是  你和艾米丽进展到什么程度了
The real question is, where are you with Emily?
这点很难说
Uh, it's hard to say.
我们进展不错  但今天发生的事
I think we're good, but things like this
让我开始考虑艾米丽是否是我的真命天女
make me wonder if Emily's really the right person for me.
你们俩曾经怀疑过对方是你的真爱吗
I mean, did you guys ever have doubts about each other?
-从来没有  -当然有过
- No. Never. - Absolutely.
什么
What?
华仔  你忘了我们刚开始约会时
Howie, you forget how much of our early dates
你总是在变魔术  我总是在强颜欢笑吗
involved you doing magic and me doing this.
好吧
Fine.
那我对你也曾有过怀疑
I had reservations about you, too.
-你没有  -好吧  我没有
- No, you didn't. - No, I didn't.
总之都不重要了
Well, it doesn't matter now,
我喜欢我俩现在的状态
'cause I love how things worked out.
我也喜欢
Me, too.
你在我眼中比这朵玫瑰花更美丽
And I think you're even more beautiful than this rose.
我上次见到我姥姥时
The last time I saw my grandma,
最开心的事就是
the most exciting thing was watching
看着她的烟灰慢慢变长
the ash of her cigarette get longer
然后猜会不会直接掉到她的布丁上
and wondering if it was gonna fall in her pudding.
结果呢
Did it?
当然掉了  然后她还没发现全吃下去了
Yeah, right in there. She ate it and everything.
莱纳德和佩妮
Leonard and Penny.
莱纳德和佩妮  莱纳德和佩妮
Leonard and Penny. Leonard and Penny.
进来
Come in!
发生什么事了
What happened?
艾米走了吗
Is Amy gone?
没有  她们让我离开
No. They asked me to leave
以便她们单独聊聊
so they could speak privately.
是的  形势真是剑拔弩张
Yeah, I know. It was quite tense.
所以现在的问题是
So here's the million dollar question:
你们谁想过去把我的火车拿过来
uh, who wants to pop over there and get my trains?
好了  我决定了
All right. I've made up my mind.
我要做正确的决定  打电话给那个姑娘
I'm gonna do the right thing, call this girl,
让她知道我已经有对象了
and let her know that I'm in a relationship.
很好  目前我们听你说过
Okay, so far we've heard,
"我决定了  我要甩掉艾米丽"
"Made up my mind, I'm dumping Emily."
"我决定了  我要扮成双胞胎兄弟
"Made up my mind to date both of them
然后同时和她俩约会"
by pretending to be twin brothers."
以及"我决定了
And "Made up my mind,
先问问她们玩不玩三人行
I'll ask for a threesome
如果被拒绝了  就当成是开玩笑混过去"
and if they say no, play it off as a joke."
我要给她打电话了
I'm calling her.
"三人行"那招并没有那么可笑好吗
And the threesome didn't deserve the belly laugh it got.
你说得对
You're right.
绝对有可能发生
It could totally happen.
你好
Hello?
你好  我是拉杰
Hi. Hi. Yeah, it's Raj.
拉杰什  我们在漫画店里见过
Rajesh. We met at the comic book store.
你好啊  确定你什么时候有空了吗
Hey, what's up? Figure out what time you're free?
其实我打电话来是想说
Actually, that's why I'm calling.
我...
I, um... I just...
我得告诉你  我有女朋友了
I need to let you know that I have a girlfriend.
好的  恭喜你
Okay. Good for you.
不  不是
Well, no, no.
我是不希望让你误会
I-I didn't want to mislead you
毕竟你约我出去
after you asked me out.
我不是约你啊
I didn't ask you out.
我只是找你帮忙我写剧本
I just need help with my screenplay.
等等  你是说我们之间不来电吗
Wait, are you saying that we didn't have a vibe?
你为什么在乎来不来电
Why do you care if we have a vibe?
你都有女朋友了
You have a girlfriend.
不是吧  我都告诉你我有女朋友了
Come on! I just told you I had a girlfriend.
起码你也得客套说我们之间来电吧
The least you can do is tell me if we had a vibe.
可以  我们来电
Sure, we had a vibe.
我就知道  我们之间来电哦
I knew it. Okay, we did have a vibe.
太兴奋了
This is exciting.
我下一步干嘛
What's my next move?
你还有女朋友呢
You still have a girlfriend.
对了  说得好
Right. Good catch.
总之很抱歉浪费了你的时间
Anyway, so I'm sorry to waste your time.
还有祝你剧本写作顺利
And, uh... and good luck with your screenplay.
等一下
Hang on.
我们都是成人了
We're both adults.
出来聚聚不一定非得意味着什么呀
We can still get together without it meaning anything.
我不行  自从你承认我们之间来电后
Not me. Ever since you admitted we had a vibe,
我已经开始策划我们的婚礼了
I've been planning our wedding.
听着  只是喝杯咖啡
Look, it's just coffee.
我只会问你一些科学问题
I'll ask you some questions about science,
我发誓  如果你求婚  我一定拒绝
and if you propose, I promise to say no.
行吧  虽然有点伤人  但行吧
Okay. That hurts a little, but okay.
很好  我会给你发信息
Great. I'll text you.
再见
Bye.
好了
All right.
我们会像成年人那样  见面喝个咖啡
So, uh, we're meeting for coffee like two adults.
大家都满意  没啥大不了
Everybody's happy. Easy peasy.
你准备告诉艾米丽吗
Are you gonna tell Emily?
当然了
Yeah, of course.
我们之间没有秘密
We have no secrets.
你准备什么时候告诉艾米丽
When are you gonna tell Emily?
奶油奶酪的事他撒谎了
He lied about the cream cheese!
整块都被他吃了  我看到了
He ate the whole thing! I saw him!
听着  我知道你认为我不适合谢尔顿
Look, I know you think I'm not right for Sheldon,
但相信我  他找不到更好的了
but trust me, I'm his best shot.
你根本不知道我忍受了些什么
You have no idea how much I put up with!
我比你更清楚
I know more than you think I do.
是吗  你知道就因为谷歌换字体
Really? You know what it's like to have date night ruined
约会之夜就被毁了的滋味吗
because Google changed their font?
小姑娘
Young lady,
如果你认为我不了解
if you think I don't know what it's like
跟一个顽固自大的人一起生活是什么感觉
to live with a stubborn, egotistical man,
那你就错了
then you're wrong.
因为我老公就是那德行
'Cause that was my husband.
是吗
Really?
有时候我真想给他的口袋里塞满玉米
There were days I wanted to fill his pockets with corn
然后扔他进猪圈  杀他个尸骨无存
and toss him in the pigpen.
既然你都了解
Well, if you understand,
为什么还要为难我呢
then why are you giving me such a hard time?
因为当初你和谢尔顿分手
Because when you broke up with Sheldon,
深深地伤害了他
it hurt him deeply,
我不希望再发生一次这种事
and I don't want to see that happen again.
抱歉
Hi. Sorry.
谢尔顿有些话想对你们说
Sheldon would like to say something to you.
没有  我没有
No, I wouldn't.
赶紧进来
Just get in here.
你们好
Hello.
去吧
Go ahead.
姥姥  听着
Meemaw, look,
我很抱歉  但是...
I'm sorry, but...
我必须替我女朋友说几句
I have to defend my girlfriend to you.
谢尔顿  谢谢你
Oh, Sheldon, thank you.
这下好  你要一把鼻涕一把泪了
Oh, great, now you're gonna get emotional.
我一直都很尊敬你和姥爷
I always looked up to you and Pop-Pop.
我知道他这个人有多难搞
I-I know what a challenging man he could be,
但我看到的是  你在他身边
but I saw you stand by him
让他变成更好的人
and-and make him into a better person.
确实是
I did.
正是如此  所以过去五年中
Yeah, well, that is exactly
我也是这样做的
what I've been doing the last five years
帮这个小麻烦一点点进步
with this little work in progress.
永远让人目瞪口呆  对吧
He never disappoints, does he?
我觉得谢尔顿想说的是
I think what Sheldon means to say is
我们一起成长
we've both grown together.
对不对
Isn't that right?
-说对  -对
- Say yes. - Yes.
好吧
Fine.
既然你如此坚持  我不会阻拦你
If you feel so strongly, I won't stand in your way.
谢谢
Thank you.
所以如果他想把那枚订婚戒指给我
So if he wanted to give me that engagement ring,
你会祝福我们吗
we would have your blessing?
大概吧
I suppose.
我才把童子之身给了你  女人
I just gave you my virginity, woman.
别那么猴急
Cool your jets.
对  你看  如果你把故事改成
Yeah, see, if you just change the story
我们星系的毁灭
to the destruction of our galaxy,
那么超级大质量黑洞就可以说得通
then a super massive black hole could work.
太棒了
This is great.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
我得想出一种
I just got to figure out a way for everyone
既不吓到孩子  又能把人都写死的方法
to die that isn't too scary for children.
那就是老爸老妈的浪漫史
And that's how Mommy and Daddy met.
你有没有跟艾米丽说我们的事
Hey, did you ever tell Emily about us?
我会说的
I will!